truckandtrailer.co.za 2017-11-14

# Privacy Statement

## Privacy Statement from Alli-Cat Publishing (Pty) Ltd., Registration Number 2002/025202/07, t/a AutoMart and Truck and Trailer (herein after referred to as "The Company")

The Company website comprises various web pages and verticals, amongst others, AutoMart and Truck and Trailer.

The Company is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Company website and governs data collection and usage. By using the Company website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

### COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

The Company collects personally identifiable information during the optional registration and ad placement processes, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. The Company also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your postal code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favourites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by the Company. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by The Company for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Company website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through the Company public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: The Company does not read any of your private online communications.

The Company encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from the Company website so that you can understand how those web ites collect, use and share your information. The Company is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Company website and the Company family of websites.

### USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

The Company collects and uses your personal information to operate the Company website and deliver the services you have requested. The Company also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from the Company and its affiliates. The Company may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

The Company does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. The Company may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, The Company may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to the Company, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

The Company may, from time to time, use any information you have submitted on any of the company sites, including but not limited to Junk Mail, Job Mail, Auto Mart, Truck & Trailer, and AgriMag, to send you marketing material that might be relevant to you.

The Company can, from time to time, also collect and use your information, collected while you browse the website, for current and future marketing purposes.

The Company does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

The Company keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within the Company website, in order to determine what services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customised content and advertising within the Company website to customers whose behaviour indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

The Company websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on The Company or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of the Company; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Company website, or the public.

### USE OF COOKIES

The Company uses "cookies" to help you personalise your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalise any of the pages on the Company website, or register with the Company site or services, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customised on the Company website.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Company website services or other websites you visit.

### SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

The Company secures your personal information from unauthorised access, use or disclosure. The Company secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorised access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

### THIRD PARTY COOKIES

The Company use both our own (first party) and partner companies' (third party) cookies to support these activities. First party cookies are owned & created by the website you're viewing. Third party cookies are owned & created by an independent company, usually a company providing a service to the website owners. Examples of usages for third party cookies are web analysis (e.g. Google Analytic) and search queries.

The Company takes due care when selecting 3rd Party service providers, however the Company cannot take responsibility for the content and use of the cookies deployed by such 3rd parties. You again have the ability within your browser to specifically deny 3rd party cookies.

### CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT

the Company will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. the Company encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how the Company is protecting your information.

### CONTACT INFORMATION

The Company welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that the Company has not adhered to this Statement, please contact us at [support@allicatpublishing.co.za](mailto:support@allicatpublishing.co.za) We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
